omb10.com 2014-08-25

# Privacy Policy | Construtor de Site

### 1. General Priniciples

ATTENTION: This privacy policy describes how OMB10 collects and uses personal information provided on our website:www.omb10.com, as well as describes the options available in respect of our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

The OMB10.com Editor was developed so that you can create and share web content with your friends, as well as create websites for your business and services, understand the simplicity, limitations and possible operational failures of our tool.

### 2. Acceptance

When you use or access OMB10, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy and also described in the terms of use and acceptance of omb10.

This privacy statement covers all and any action on the site [www.omb10.com](http://www.omb10.com/). If you, as a user or customer, have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you must first get in contact with our privacy team, by address [abuse@omb10.com](mailto:abuse@OMB10.com).

​

### 3. Collection and protection of information and the content

As the majority of websites, when using the site OMB10.com, you provide two types of information: limited personal information and content information (that, fully aware, you choose to disclose and/or post it on the site OMB10.com).

Upon entering OMB10.com, we use objects for tracking partners of third parties to collect the type of browser and IP address you use by log files. This information is collected for all visitors of OMB10.com. In addition, we store certain information from your browser using "cookies". By default, we use a persistent cookie that stores your login id and password to make your login easier when you return to OMB10.com. You can remove or block this cookie using the settings of your browser, if you want to disable this convenient feature.

​

### 4. Billing Information

When you sign up for OMB10.com we will ask for your billing information, along with other information such as name, telephone number, and address, to process the transaction and charge the fees involved.

We do not store your billing information, and this information will be discarded after the processing of your transaction.

​

### 5. Sharing content with third parties

We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

The OMB10.com provides, as its main service, the ability to share content created on the internet with other users, friends and people in your networks.

We can provide you with the information and/or the personal content of the user to service providers to help us provide the services that we offer. Specifically, we may use third parties to facilitate our business, such as hosting the service on a secondary site for servers, offer you our community blog, send updates about OMB10.com by e-mail, removing repetitive information from our lists of users and process payments for products or services and to offer you our live chat services. In the context of these commercial operations, our service providers may have access to your personal information and/or content for use by a limited amount of time in connection with such business activities. When you register for our services, we will share our personal information only when necessary to ensure that the third party can offer that service.

Occasionally, we provide statements of user-created content to allow the non-users to have an idea of what occurs in OMB10.com. This content is provided in a manner that protects its contents from any edition and/or unauthorized alteration.

We may be required to disclose your personal information in accordance with legal requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, or in accordance with the applicable laws. Only disclose information when we believe, in good faith, that a request for information by law enforcement or private litigation meets the relevant legal standards. In addition, we may share account information or other information when we believe it is necessary to comply with the law, to protect our interests or property, to prevent fraud or other illegal activity perpetrated through the service of OMB10.com or using the name OMB10.com, or avoid imminent physical damage. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, agents, or government agencies. 

### 6\. Announcements of OMB10

We use your email address to send promotional messages and important announcements. If you no longer wish to receive these emails, please follow the unsubscribe instructions contained in promotional communications you receive. 

### 7\. Links

OMB10.com may contain links to other web sites. Of course, we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. We encourage our users to be cautious, when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of all sites that collect personal information. This privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by OMB10.com or posted on the site OMB10.com. 

​

### 8. Public Forums

Our web site offers a forum for discussion of issues relevant to the use of the tool OMB100. You should be aware that any information provided in these areas can be read, collected and used by others that they access. 

​

### 9. Social Media Widgets

Our website includes social media features such as, the Facebook button and Widgets, These features may collect your IP address, which page you're visiting our web site and may set up a cookie to enable the feature to operate correctly. The social media features and widgets are hosted by a third party or directly from our site. Your interactions with these resources are governed by the privacy policy of the company that is providing. 

### 10. Altering or Removing Content

The access and control over the personal content in OMB10.com are possible through the tools for editing content. Users of OMB10.com may modify or delete any content at any time by logging into their account. Any changes will be updated immediately. Users who want to disable the account of OMB10.com can do this from the My account page. 

We will retain your information while your account is active or the time necessary to provide our services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and monitor the compliments of our agreements. 

​

### 11. Security

OMB10.com takes appropriate precautions to protect the information and the content of our users. We have safeguards, physical and electronic procedures to protect your account information and content that is uploaded. 

Sensitive Information (such as credit card numbers) do not pass through our system, being these are manipulated by outsourced companies and public reputability. 

### ﻿​12. Terms of Use, Notices and Revisions

What you make using OMB10.com, and any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy, as well as to our general Terms of Use and acceptance, and to all of its provisions, including disclaimer of warranty, limitation of liability, indemnification and choice of law. We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes in our information practices. If we make any material changes, we will inform you by e-mail (to the address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this site before the change is to be effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. Unless otherwise specified, our privacy policy applies to all of the information that we have about you and for any one of your accounts. 

### ﻿​13. Contact with the site

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please get in contact with us by [contact@omb10.com](mailto:contact@OMB10.com)
